Hello, my name is Nagi Inoue.
Today I am dressed like this...
Well, here I am!
I'd like to cook!
Yay!
I've been working on a project under construction before.
I've cooked for the New Year's holidays.
I've cooked for you before.
I want to show everyone that I can cook well
I hope I can show you all that I can cook well too.
I will do my best.
Well then, thank you very much for watching.
Now, I would like to announce what we are going to cook today.
Here you go!
Fried shrimp. Fried shrimp.
I'm going to make fried shrimp today, but I thought it would be a little bit boring if I make a normal fried shrimp.
My name is Nagi, which is Japanese for Japanese style, so I'm going to make fried prawns with a Japanese twist.
Well, I hope you are looking forward to seeing how it turns out!
Let's go!
Okay, I'm going to take the heads off the prawns.
And then I'm going to peel the shells off, but the head part also has some kind of miso or soup stock in it, so I want to use that part too.
So I'd like to use that part as well.
Okay, wait a minute.
Wow! Wow! There's so much miso inside!
But my father was allergic to shrimp, so we didn't eat much shrimp at home.
But I loved it so much that I used to eat it by myself.
But when I decided to make fried shrimp in Japanese style like this, I actually bought it.
I actually bought some, and it was so much fun to peel them.
So, I want to take off the back cotton.
The back cotton is in the back part, you know.
Cut a slit in the back.
Oh, I found it!
I can do it like this.
Remove the back cotton and process it.
If you leave it like this, the shrimp will curl up.
I'm going to cut a slit here.
Okay, now, when we fry them up, they should be straight.
Are these shrimp called "shako" or something like that?
I like Terraformers, and there's a character named Cage.
I like Terraformers, and there's a character named Cage, and his character's ability is to eat mantis shrimps.
I heard that shrimp have a very fishy smell, so I'm going to take the smell out.
I'm going to use a little alcohol.
Okay, now, let it sit for about five minutes, five, ten minutes.
That's it. Thank you very much for watching.
Okay, so here we go.
So, I'm going to take the exuviae?
I'd like to start with the, uh, the exuviae.
Jyan!
Put the men-tsuyu into the pot first.
When I made it at home, I made it without reading the directions.
When I made it at home, I didn't read the directions, but the mentsuyu was so thick that I made a mistake.
I want to make sure to dilute it properly.
So, in this
Wow, there is a lot of miso!
I'm going to put this in, too, and simmer it.
Stew it?
I think it's more like "take out the broth".
Next...
I think fried prawns should have tartar, but tartar has mayonnaise in it.
I was wondering if I could somehow make it Japanese style, so I'm going to use white miso this time.
I'm going to use white miso and yuzu to make it look a little bit like tartar.
First of all, we're going to add sake to the white miso.
Put about 2 tablespoons of sake.
Now add sugar.
There you go.
If you put a little bit more sugar, it will make it sweeter.
Mix it in.
There you go.
Now put the egg in.
If you put an egg in, it becomes a very beautiful yellow color.
It's cracked!
And then mix the yolk in too.
Now, mix the yolk with the egg.
It turns into a beautiful yellow color.
Doesn't it look a bit like tartar?
Looks delicious!
Next, I'm going to take out the yuzu and squeeze out the scraps.
I'll go cut it up.
Here we go.
It smells so good!
I don't know...
I'm going to squeeze the yuzu with a fork.
Oh, wow!
That's a lot of yuzu!
I looked up what is Japanese style and found that there are some important colors in Japanese food.
I found out that there are some important colors in Japanese food, and it says "red, yellow, blue, blue, green, white and black".
I wanted to achieve a little bit of yellow in the tartar tartar, so I made it very slick.
I'm sure the yuzu flavor will come into its own now.
I finished microwaving.
It gets a little bit hard in the microwave.
It's a little bit thicker than before.It's getting slower than before.
I like it.
When I squeezed the yuzu...
Maybe it got in my eyes.
My eyes hurt like hell.
I put some drops in my eyes.
While I was microwaving...
I cried a lot.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh!
Here.
Here you go.
Here we go, let's mix it up!
Now it looks a lot more tartar-like.
Now that the sauce is done, let's move on to the main dish.
I'll move on to the main part.
This one looks good, too!
I've probably finished prepping the shrimp by now.
I'm going to rub them with salt.
Rub them with salt.
And I'm going to leave this one here for a while.
Okay.
And this one...
It's hail!
I think I'm going to use breadcrumbs for the batter this time.
But I thought breadcrumbs are not Japanese style.
So I decided to use arare.
Then, make the batter liquid.
Here we go!
There you go!
I want to use rice flour to make the butter liquid.
I want to use rice flour, about three times a spoonful.
And an egg, or something.
But it's not too much, it's just right.
Then we dip the shrimp in it, dip them in the arule, and fry them.
I'll use fireworks.
Okay.
This is the part I'm most nervous about.
I made a mistake once, and it was a little difficult.
I bought these five-color arabesques.
There's white, orange, yellow, green, and red.
But orange is not one of the five colors I explained earlier.
But I'm sure it will be very colorful and look good.
Okay, I'll go put it on.
I'm going to put it on.
Put a lot of butter liquid on it.
There we go.
It should look good.
Look how cute it is! Here we go!
Wow! Sounds good!
Wow! Cute!
It's gonna be good.
Oh!
I forgot one thing. There's a little step I forgot to do.
I'll get to it later.
Here we go.
Wow, it's so cute! It looks good!
And the step I forgot... it's very important.
The shrimp's... tail is drained.
When we did it at home, they were soaked in water, so when we put them in the oil, they bounced around.
So they bounced around a lot, and it hurt a lot.
We're going to remove the head.
We cut it off with this.
We let the water out like this.
Now it's drained.
Okay, now we're back to the process.
Grasshopper juice and
And the hail.
It's not very common to buy just hail.
That's why my mother
When she was making the prototypes
from ochazuke (rice with green tea) to arabesque.
Awww...
She said she thought I could make a lot of money if I had this kind of food.
Okay, I'll go give it to her.
Throw it in!
Wow, sounds good
Wow, so beautiful
Cute.
Yes! Ta-da!
It's done!
I think the color becomes more beautiful pink when drained like this.
It's more like a salmon pink.
It's done!
Yay!
I'm so happy with how cute it looks!
Now, I'd like to eat it myself!
Bon appétit!
Let's start with the tartar!
Let's start with the tartar!(expression of) effort or strain
Oh, that looks good.
Bon appétit.
Yum! Yum!
Yum! The arare is so big that it has a strong presence and is very tasty!
I'm satisfied!
Next, the men-tsuyu!
Yes! Bon appétit!
Yum! Amazing! You know...
It tastes like miso.
Oh, this is delicious!
If you use the head of a shrimp to serve it...
I was told that there might be a little bit
I was told that it might have a bad smell.
Not at all.
Delicious!
Yum!
Well, it was a lot of fun.
I like to think about it.
What should I do with this?
What should I do with that?
What should I not use?
I was thinking about it with my mom.
It was a lot of fun.
It was fun, and I'd like to do it again.
But I couldn't stop crying forever.
I've been blinking my eyes a lot.
Please be careful!
But it was delicious, so I'm satisfied.
Subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating!
Like us!
Thank you so much!
Bye bye!
ED